我不明白
I don't get it.
打印机墨盒接二连三地发生了什么
What keeps happening to the printer cartridges?
你们偷墨了吗
Have you guys been stealing ink?
是啊  妈妈  你知道我们小孩子
Yeah, mom, you know us kids.
就是抵挡不住香甜喷墨的诱惑
We just can't resist that sweet, sweet ink.
家庭办公室里还有多余墨盒
There's a spare cartridge in the home office.
我们有家庭办公室吗
We have a home office?
不  只是爸妈这么叫
No. That's just what mom and dad call the room
那间堆满还未打包的垃圾的房间
where they keep all the crap they haven't unpacked yet.
总有一天  会成为家庭办公室的
One day, it is gonna be a home office.
我和你们父亲会有
And your father and I are gonna have
一张摆着两台电脑的大书桌
a big desk with two computers,
我会为当地报纸写一个叫做
and I write a column for the local newspaper
"黛比  可以吗"的专栏
Called "Debbie, do I?"
"亲爱的黛比  可以吗
"Dear Debbie do I,
我妈妈沉浸在一个根本不存在的
my mother has retreated into a fantasy world
家庭办公室幻想中
of nonexistent home offices.
我该怎么办
What do I do?"
好吧
All right.
快点  家人们  奔去家庭办公室
Hurry, family. To the home office.
天啊  马蒂  发生了什么
Oh, my god. Marty, what's happening?
这满办公室的水是哪来的
What is the office water come from?
我想是管子爆了
I think a pipe burst.
好吧  这房间进入人管大战
All right. It is man vs. mold in this room.
马克思  艾比  你们担任运输工作
Max, Abby, you're on hauling duty.
我要去杰克家过夜
Oh, uh...I'm supposed to go to Jack's for a sleepover.
我需要点自己的独处时间
A-and I just need some me time.
-是啊  -再见
- Yeah. - Bye.
这样吧  我帮你们把我所有的东西拿走
Here. Let me grab all my stuff for you.
谢谢你  宝贝儿
Oh, thank you, baby.
这可帮了大忙了  谢谢你
That's a big help. Thank you.
这就是我所有的东西
This is all my stuff.
-我们这一路犯了不少错啊  -是啊
- We've made some mistakes along the way. - Yeah.
我们来自外太空  定居美国新泽西*
*We came from outer space and settled in New Jersey
出售中
我们取名拉里・伯德和杰西・乔伊娜-柯西*
*We took names like Larry Bird and Jackie Joyner-Kersee
接着有人类搬到隔壁*
*Then the humans moved next door
不断挑战我们的极限*
*Started testing all our limits
各位看官请上座  演出开始了*
*So sit right down, enjoy the show
外星邻居 第二季 第十集
30分钟就搞定*
*We'll be done in 30 minutes
旅行日程
把它移走  棒棒糖
Scoot job, lollipop.
我得把我今日要投的简历打出来
I need to print out my daily batch of résumés
"伯德-柯西家庭的快乐一天"
"Bird-kersee family fun day"?
你这是把墨浪费在些什么破玩意上
What's this drivel you're wasting our ink on?
首先  你清楚地知道
First of all, you know very well
这墨是你从韦弗家偷来的
that you stole that ink from the Weavers.
第二  这是我为我父母计划的
Second, these are the itineraries
特别日子旅行日程
for the special day I have planned for my parents.
我要带他们去看我在地球上最喜欢的地方
I'm going to show them my favorite places on earth,
最后到隐山购物商场的停车场
ending with the hidden hills mall parking lot,
-在那我们要...  -等等
- Where we will... - Wait.
你要带他们来我们的停车场
You're taking them to our parking lot?
难道我们就不能有秘密吗
Is nothing secret?
做你想做的  但别拉上我
Do what you want, but leave me out of it.
也指望我为你那对
And don't expect me to pick up the pieces
丢下你的嬉皮老好人父母收拾残局
when your hippie, do-gooder parents desert you
无论他们这周接下来用什么疯狂的理由
for whatever their next crazy cause of the week is.
"真高兴见到你  女儿
"Nice seeing you, daughter.
我们现在得丢下你
We have to abandon you now
去帮个受了伤的火星人
to help a Martian with a boo-boo."
模仿得真像  女婿
Spot-on impression, son-in-law.
明显他用大把时间来学这个
He's obviously had a lot of free time to work on it.
工作找得怎么样了
So, how is the job hunting going?
今天  我申请了高盛集团营销副总裁
Today, I'm applying to be V.P. Of marketing at GOLDMAN SACHS,
摩根史坦利投资公司的首席财务官
CFO at Morgan Stanley,
美国最著名的意大利餐厅Babbo的主厨和共有者
马利欧・巴塔利新餐厅的主厨职位
Head chef at Mario Batali's new restaurant.
考虑到你出身殷实
Seems as if you're aiming a little high,
在这星球上又无工作经验
considering you're a trust-fund baby
你定的目标可有点高啊
with zero work experience on this planet.
我觉得入门级的工作比较适合你
I think an entry-level job would be good for you.
就像普通人一样  别带那么高帽
Make you feel less entitled, like one of the people.
"普通人"吗  恶心透顶
"The people"? Gross.
我是个美貌与智慧并存的最高领袖
I am a supreme leader with a grace and intellect
美国演员  鲍德温兄弟四人皆为演员
还具有亚历克・鲍德温
and that certain "X" Factor
不同于史蒂芬・鲍德温的完美品质
that separates the Alec Baldwins from the Stephen Baldwins.
有几个公司给你回信了
Have you had any responses to your applications?
-给"几个"是多少  -一个
- Define "Any." - One.
按你们严格的定义来说  没有
Well, given your stringent definition, no.
但谁说你要收到邀请
But who says you need to wait for an invitation
才能去面试
to get a job interview?
每个人都这么说
Everyone.
好吧  你们这些居高临下的废物恶魔
All right, you condescending boho devils,
下次我走过这扇门
the next time I walk through that door,
我一定有工作了
I shall have a job.
亲爱的  他还穿着浴袍
Darling, he's still wearing his bathrobe.
给他点时间
Just give him a moment.
这不算数
Doesn't count.
我没从门进来
I didn't come through the door.
关德斯丹得广告公司
我是来面征创意总监的
I'm here to become your new creative director.
我要求薪水八位数
So, I'm looking for eight figures.
我直话直说了  总薪金要七位
And I'll be direct -- I want them all to be a seven.
特拉维斯&埃克勒&罗克尼联合律师事务所
用三个词形容我自己
Describe myself in three words?
算数不好
Not good at counting.
我对时尚和杂志有着无比的热情
I have a passion for fashion and a passion for magazines.
我有个问题
Um, I do have one question.
念"Vo-gay" 还是"Vo-gooey"
Is it pronounced "Vo-gay" Or "Vo-gooey"?
特拉维斯&埃克勒&罗克尼联合律师事务所
我最大的缺点  浪漫喜剧
My greatest weakness? Romantic comedies.
你刚刚是不是按了紧急按钮
Did you just hit a panic button?
你按了  我看见了
You did! I saw you!
这就是为何我觉得
And that is why I do not think
J.D.塞林格的最新小说《麦田里的守望者》
J.D. Salinger's latest novel, 'the catcher in the rye,'
不会和年轻读者产生共鸣的原因
is going to resonate with young readers."
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
就是看些初中时代的小破玩意
Just looking through some lame middle-school stuff.
我也许应该丢掉它们
I'm probably gonna throw it all away.
天啊
Oh, my god.
这是我第一次偷看
This is the candy I bought
限制级电影时买的糖
when I snuck into my first R-rated movie.
我们就随便坐在某个老男人身边
We sat next to some random old guy.
当引座员经过的时候
And when the usher passed by,
我就说"爸爸  把爆米花给我"
I was like, "Dad, pass the popcorn."
帅爆了
It was totally awesome.
但之后  他就问我要号码
And then afterwards, he asked for my number,
就没那么好了
which was less awesome.
我不敢相信你看过
I cannot believe you saw a movie
美国电影协会
that the Motion Picture Association of America
限制你看的电影
did not approve for you!
这是我第一场演唱会的票
These are from my first concert.
我们得从围栏下钻过
We had to sneak in under the fence
才能进入贵宾区
to get into the V.I.P. area.
我们相遇之前你的生活真精彩
You have so many cool stories from before we met.
有一次  万圣节的时候
One time, I dressed up
我打扮得像一箱鸡蛋
like a carton of eggs for Halloween.
我知道  一个月前的事  当时我在场
I know. It was a month ago. I was there.
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
几年前
Okay, so, a few years ago,
我和我朋友溜进了休・杰克曼拍的
my friend and I snuck into Hugh Jackman's trailer
休・杰克曼:澳洲动作巨星
和机器人对打那部电影的拖车里
on the set of that fighting-robot movie.
真是个帅哥
What a nice guy.
真是太棒了
Crazy cool.
我按地理坐标排列了所有我喜欢的地方
So, I have arranged all my favorite places by geographical location
然后给每个活动分配了半个小时
and allotted one half-hour per activity.
最后几页空白的是用来贴照片的
The last few pages are blank for scrapbooking!
布特库思能参加你们的欢乐一日游吗
Can the Butkus get in on your day of fun?
亲爱的  我不确定你能不能跟得上
Oh, darling, I'm just not sure you can keep up.
拜托了  美女  至少让我穿上鞋子
Puh-lease, girl. Let me just put on my kicks.
小兔子穿过了地下隧道
The baby rabbit goes through the tunnel
越过了小树  不
and over the log and-- no!
翻过围墙  越过小树
Over the fence and through the log
穿过隧道
and under the tunnel.
不
No!
小兔子在树旁乱跑...
The baby rabbit goes around the log...
好好玩吧
Have a great day.
我去拿外套
I'll just get my coat.
我们来张自拍吧
Let's do a selfie.
孙子  你头发看起来没平时那么翘了
Grandson, your hair looks a little less proud than usual.
-怎么了  -韦弗一家发大水了
- Is something wrong? - The Weavers had a flood,
让我意识到我没有什么精彩的经历
and they made me realize I've got no cool stories.
但我一定会想出一个快要害死我的一个
But I'm gonna come up with one if it kills me.
迪克  和我一起[也有侧踢的意思]
Dick, sidekick me.
谢你啊  现在过来帮忙
Thank you. Now come help me.
他刚才是说韦弗一家发大水了吗
Did he just say the Weavers had a flood?
是的
Yes, he did.
也许我们应该去看看
Perhaps we should go check on them.
-他们也许需要我们的帮忙  -太棒了
- They may need our help. - Yes!
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
他们人呢
Where are they?
也许这算是个好事  你知道吗
Maybe it's good that this happened, you know?
让我们能重新彻底的整理家庭办公室
Help us get the home office on its feet.
绝对是  有老鼠
Oh, totally. There's a mouse!
那边有只死老鼠在玩水上漂
It's a dead mouse floating over there.
弄走它  弄走它
Power through. Power through!
这是我原来的联盟棒球手套
Hey! This is my old little-league mitt!
我还记得那天我爸爸给我时的情形
I remember the day my dad gave me this.
他说  "给你  小笨蛋
He said, "Here you go, moron.
"也许这手套有助于你比赛  因为现在
"Maybe this glove will help your game, because right now,
"我看不出你是在打外场
"I can't tell if you're playing the outfield
还是在出柜"
or coming out of the closet."
是啊  他是个好人
Mm. Yeah, he's sweet.
有人吗  有人吗  大家还好吗
Hello, hello! Is everybody okay in here?
伙计们  我们很好  我们很好
Oh, hey, guys. Yeah, we're fine. We're fine.
别想说几句话就把我们赶走
Don't try to talk us out of it.
我们是来帮忙的  我们擅长处理洪水
We're here to help. Floods are kind of our thing.
让我猜猜  你是来面试的
Let me guess-- job interview.
和很多人一样
One of many.
我也是
Me, too.
这些公司根本不知道
These companies are incapable of realizing
我能给他们带来多少好处
how much I have to offer.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it!
我上了四年大专
I went to junior college for four years,
而这些人力资源部的代表却问这种问题
and these H.R. Reps keep being like,
"你想在收发室里干活吗"
"Want to work in the mailroom?"
不  粉碎梦想的大魔头  我不想
No, dream killer, I don't.
我再也不想应聘这些弱爆了的工作了
I'm done applying for lame jobs.
我不是那种"从底层做起"的人
I'm not a "Work your way up" kind of guy.
我可是扎克伯格一样
I'm a Zuckerberg.
扎克伯格:Facebook创始人
我也是  但是有文克莱沃斯的身
Oh, me, too, but in the body of a Winklevoss.
文克莱沃斯:扎克伯格校友  起诉扎克伯格并获赔
显而易见
No need to state the obvi.
我叫拉菲
I'm Raffi.
我叫拉里
Larry.
你应该和我一起去咖啡店见见我的朋友
You should come hang out with me and my buddies at the coffee shop.
他们有最便宜的危地马拉冰啤
They have the best fair-trade Guatemalan cold brew.
你有兴趣吗
You insky?
老实说
Got to be honest.
你说的话我大概只听懂了三分之一
I'm only getting maybe one out of every three words,
但是  拉菲  我太感兴趣了
but, Raffi, I am so insky.
拉里  这就是我的朋友们
Larry, this is my crew.
-哟 -哟
- Zip.  - Zip.
这就是我们工作的地方
And this is where we work.
你是做咖啡的
You make coffee?
做咖啡  不  发关于咖啡的东西  马上
Make coffee? No. Blog about coffee? Soon.
你知道网页设计师吗
You know a good web designer?
你是说你在这里坐一整天
You mean you just stay here all day,
做自己的事情  看起来轻松又酷炫
working on your own stuff, looking effortlessly cool?
差不多吧
Eh, pretty much.
这才是我的小伙伴们
My people.
拉里・伯德  和那个篮球运动员一样
Larry Bird, like the basketball player.
莫莱  和那个酱名字一样
Mole? Like the sauce.
莫莱:墨西哥一种用巧克力制作而成的近乎黑色的调味酱
这是我的照片博客
This is my photo blog.
我给创口贴写了三行诗
I write haikus on band-aids,
然后我把它们写在身上  给自己拍照
then I put them on my body and photograph myself.
所以  我做什么都可以
So, I can work on anything,
哪怕和莫莱的一样不知所谓
even if it's stupid like Mole's thing?
天哪  莫莱啊
Holy Mole?
我应该给我的博客起这个名字的
That's what I should have named my blog.
撑着门
All right, hold the door.
伙计们  我们租了一个真空吸湿器
Okay, guys, we rented a wet vac.
怎么了  伙计们
What's going on, guys?
我们根据我们原来帮助
Well, we came up with a rudimentary organizational system
木星上熔岩海啸受难者的经历
based on what we used to help the victims
想出了这个基本组织系统
of the lava tsunami on jupiter.
黛比  我找到了一张你和马蒂的照片
And, Debbie, I found this picture of you and Marty.
-你还穿着白裙子呢  -是的
- And you're in a white dress. - Oh, yes.
那是我们结婚时拍的
Oh, that's our wedding.
我妈妈觉得这条裙子有点夸张了
My mom thought the dress was a bit too much
发型也让我看起来很疯狂
and the hairdo made me seem desperate.
你看起来完美极了
You look perfect!
-我有吗  -看看你嫁的这个人
- I do? - Hey, and check out that stud you're marrying.
真不知道你身上发生了啥
I don't know what happened to you!
我知道  我知道  我爸爸说我一到30岁
I know. I know. My dad says once I hit 30
我就会发福  所以...
that I lost what little looks I had, so...
我本来是想说你变帅了的
Well, I was gonna say you've only gotten handsomer.
什么  小黛  怎么了
What? Deb, what's happening?
我觉得  如果你父母都很好
Well, I think this is what it's like
或父母很清醒的话  就该是这样的
when you have good parents, or at least ones that are sober.
你们在这里啊  我到处找你们
There you are. I've been looking all over.
如果我们现在动身的话
If we leave now,
就可以在洗车场关门之前去一趟
we can go through the car wash before it closes.
简直像重生
It's like being born.
亲爱的  我觉得我们今天不能去
Uh, sweetheart, I don't think we're gonna be able
参观你在地球上的最爱的地方了
to tour your favorite places on earth today.
-韦弗家遭洪水了  -他们需要我们
- You see, the Weavers had a flood. - They need us.
不然我们明天再做这些好吗
Maybe we could do your day tomorrow, hmm?
当然  再等一天也无妨
Of course. What's another day?
我也来帮忙吧
And maybe if I pitch in,
这样早点完成  也许还有时间再去参观
we can finish up in time to do a few of the things on my list.
太好了
Yes!
我四年级的成绩报告单
Oh, oh, my fourth-grade report card!
你能不能看看这些A  说点什么
Could you look at all the As and say something
除了"别让男孩们知道你多聪明"
besides "Don't tell boys you're smart"?
你喜欢冒险型还是安全型
Now, do you want the safe option or the risky option?
恶作剧电话要是安全
The prank call didn't become
人气就不可能这么高了
a crazy-story staple by playing it safe.
冒险型
Risky me.
-你好  -女士您好
- Hello? - Hello, ma'am?
-您有女儿吗  -对
- Do you have a daughter? - Yes.
她刚刚遭遇了一场可怕的交通事故
Well, she's been in a horrible car accident.
不不  当我没说
Uh, no, never mind.
-不  她没有  -你到底在说什么
- No, no, she hasn't. - What are you talking about?
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
迪克  你怎么回事
Dick, what's wrong with you?
我心理很阴暗的
I'm a dark, little dude.
你们分类整理的如何啦
How's the sorting going out there?
人呢
Hello?
妈妈  爸爸
Mommy? Daddy?
本人穿起来更漂亮
Even more beautiful in person.
真的吗
Really?
看我穿白色  你会不会在想
And seeing me in white, you're not thinking,
"你到底想骗谁  黛比拉"
"Who are you trying to fool, Deborah?"
我都不知道那是什么意思  亲爱的
I don't even know what that means, sweetheart.
你是世界上最好的妈妈
You're the best mom.
是啊  看看多漂亮
Yeah! Look at you.
其实  虽然我没见过其他人扔棒球
Now, you know, I may have never seen anybody throw a baseball before,
不过你刚刚那绝对是完美的一击
but if that wasn't perfect form, I don't know what is.
谢谢您  乔伊娜-柯西先生
Well thank you, Mr. Joyner-Kersee.
拜托  马蒂
Oh, come on, Marty.
叫我的扎波隆名字吧
Call me by my Zabvronian name.
叫老爸
It's Daddy.
这个嘛
Oh, well, you know what?
可能会有一点奇怪
That would probably be a little bit weird
因为在地球上的意思是...
Because here on earth, that means --
-接得不错  马蒂  -谢谢  老爸
- Great catch, Marty! - Thanks, Daddy!
你居然打算这样做
I can't believe you're doing this.
-媒体上会全是绯闻的  -我知道
- It's got scandal written all over it. - I know.
不过麦莉・赛勒斯教会了我
But as Miley Cyrus taught me,
想有好故事  绝对不能穿衣服
you don't get a good story by keeping your clothes on.
来吧
Let's do this!
哥哥  不要啊
Brother, don't!
我成功了
I'm doing it.
我在裸泳
I'm skinny dipping!
其实  这情景没我想得震撼
Turns out, this is not an "Omg" Moment.
穿好衣服  流浪汉
Cover up, tramp.
我决定在微博客展示一下[社交分享网站]
I've decided to work on a Tumblr
怎样才能优雅  睿智
about how to have the grace, intellect,
拥有卓越领袖的能力
and "X" Factor of a supreme leader.
"这些只能与生俱来
"You're either born with an 'x' factor or you aren't,
所以努力生好点吧"
so try to be born with it."
太棒了
Ooh, that is epic!
等等
Wait a minute.
连接错误
无法连接到网络
怎么回事  我的人生建议网站不见了
What -- what happened to my life-advice website?
试用时间结束了
Your trial period expired.
新规定是  五美元消费
There's a new policy where you only get
可以换得一小时的无线网络使用时间
an hour of Wi-fi for every $5 purchase,
所以得充值了  兄弟
so time to muffin up, hombre.
我应该跟谁反映
Who do I talk to about this?
我是拉里・伯德
I am larry bird,
"像我一样卓越"网站的财务总监
CFO, president, and sole subscriber
董事长  以及唯一用户
of the website "Supreme like me,"
也是Hollymolly网站的资深顾问
as well as consulting producer of Holymolly.org.
我有权免费使用wifi
And I deserve free wi-fi!
这里的规矩不是我定的
Look, I don't make the rules around here.
买一杯咖啡  我就把密码给你
You buy a cup of coffee, I give you a slip.
好吧  这是你逼我的
Fine. You're going to force my hand.
大家都免费用吧
Free internet for everyone!
快来拿密码
Come get your password!
无线网络送给你
Viva la wi-fi! Ha ha!
这是wifi密码  不需要任何消费
Here's a wi-fi password. No purchase necessary.
博客里写到我时  写好点
When you blog about me, blog well.
wifi密码
Wi-fi password.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the hell's going on here?
有免费wifi的美好世界  你谁啊
Just free wi-fi utopia. Who are you?
-老板  -是吗
- The owner. - Oh.
抱歉  艾伦
Uh, sorry about that, Alan.
这样吧  给所有人来杯拿铁寄我老爹账上
Here. Put a round of lattes on my old man.
-应该可以抵消免费网络的费用吧  -什么
- That should cover the free internet. - What?
你爸爸给了你一张信用卡
You have a credit card from your father?
是啊
Uh, yeah.
我们大多都这样  不然怎么付钱
Most of us do. That's how we pay for stuff.
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
你们这些被宠坏的富二代
You' just a bunch of spoiled, rich kids
只会啃父母的钱
living off your parents!
怪不得找不到工作
No wonder you can't find jobs!
你们这群臭小子
You lazy, self-entitled...
懒惰无用  自恋至极
trust-fund brats.
说得真狠  我才34岁
Harsh, man, I am only 34.
听着  这都是我干的
Listen, this is all my doing.
我最近很不顺  我岳父岳母搬来了
I've had a tough time lately. My in-laws have moved in.
而且我失业了
I'm unemployed.
由于冬天  我的头发很干
Winter's really drying out my hair.
兄弟  出来讨生活的
Look, pal, you're not the only one
不只你一个
out there trying to make it.
大家都不容易  好吗
It's tough out there for everyone, all right?
我孩子上高中  每个月
I got a high-schooler who can't seem to stay
要发上千条短信
under a thousand texts a month,
我刚刚花了五百元
and I just dropped a half a grand
送我家小孩去参加贾斯汀・比伯的音乐会
taking my littlest to the Justin Bieber concert.
不过至少她抓到了他的背心  那可是无价的
But at least she caught his tank top, so priceless!
我孩子花费也很多
I, too, have expensive children.
如果钱买不到幸福  怎么不告诉我家孩子
If money can't buy you happiness, no one told my kids.
是啊  我就是这意思
Well, yeah, that's what I'm talking about, you know?
所以我才开始了新的网络规定
That's why I got the new internet policy.
不打不相识
In light of today's debacle,
我知道这话有点冒昧
I know this is a pretty long shot,
不过你还招人吗
but do you have any openings here?
我什么都可以做  你需要什么我就做什么
I'll do anything -- whatever you need.
我准备好从基层做起了
I'm ready to start at the bottom.
我的天  你在干什么呢
Oh, my god. What are you doing?
我要做件值得跟你提及的事情
I'm going to do something worth telling you about,
哪怕这事会害死我
even if it kills me!
这很有可能害死我  所以我现在就得告诉你
And it might literally kill me, so I got to tell you right now
你穿那件高翻领毛衣帅极了
that you look slamming in that turtleneck.
抱歉  我现在如此邋遢
I'm sorry for being so raunchy!
你说什么值得跟我提及的故事
What do you mean, a story worth telling me?
我没什么可以跟你说的
I have nothing to tell you,
我担心你会觉得我无聊
and I'm worried that you're gonna get bored of me!
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
雷吉  每一天
Reggie, every day,
你都会看着我觉得理所当然的东西
you look at something I take for granted
好像那就是全世界最酷的一样
like it's the coolest thing in the world.
还有  现在这样  我在屋顶下和你说话
And by the way, this right here, me talking you off a roof,
就能算是一个疯狂的故事了
this counts as a crazy story.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
我这就下来
I'll be right down.
穿着那高翻领毛衣你得小心点
And you better watch yourself in that turtleneck,
因为我一下来就要紧紧抱着你
because when I get down, I'm going to...hug you close.
这是什么
Oh. What's this?
那是”尽情吃”自助餐的礼券
Oh, that's a gift certificate to an all-you-can-eat buffet.
我妈妈给我的  因为她错过了我的毕业典礼
My mom gave it to me because she missed my graduation.
她说第二天我们要去吃顿丰富的午餐
She said that we were gonna have a big celebration lunch
庆祝一下  就我们两人
the next day, just the two of us.
简单说吧  证书还在
Oh. Well, let's just say I still have the certificate.
我相信她没去一定是有很好的理由
Oh. I'm sure there's a very good reason why she wasn't there.
一家叫做”砰砰”的卖山寨抹胸的商店
There was a fire sale at a store called Boom Boom
在搞大甩卖
that sold irregular tube tops.
再说了  我不觉得
Besides, I don't think
忽视自己的孩子会有什么好理由
there's ever a good reason to ignore your child.
你说得对
No.
丈夫
Husband!
-怎么了  -我们得走了
- What's the matter? - We have to go.
我们的乐于助人耽误了
We've let our helpfulness get in the way
我们该陪伴女儿的时间
of spending time with our daughter!
该死  总是这样
Oh, damn! This always happens!
-你们现在就要走了  是吗  -是的
- You're leaving now, aren't you? - Mm-hmm.
-但是我们需要搭个车  -我开车送你们
- But we need a ride. - Oh! I'll drive you.
老爸  你去哪了
Daddy, where did you go?!
别这样看着我
No. It's okay,
他名字就是老爸  这么叫不奇怪
because his name is Daddy, so it's not weird.
谢谢你们送我们来  韦弗夫妇
Thanks for the ride, Weavers.
不  是谢谢你们的帮忙
Well, no. Thank you for all your help.
是啊  我们那些东西都会带来糟糕的回忆
Yeah, and all that stuff we have that brought back bad memories?
现在终于有个好事了
Well, we now have good ones to go with them.
-谢谢  -晚安  你们俩
- Thank you. - Good night, guys.
-晚安  -拜
- Good night. - Bye.
-又无父无母了  -至少我们还有孩子们
- Parentless again. - Well, at least we have our kids.
-有吗  他们抛弃了我们  -是啊
- Do we? They abandoned us. - Yeah, they did.
我们的父母很糟糕  我们也变成了糟糕的父母
We had lousy parents, we became lousy parents,
现在我们的孩子也很糟糕
and now we have lousy kids.
-吃点冻酸奶吗  -必须的
- Froyo? - Always.
最后一站  隐山购物中心停车场
Last stop -- Hidden Hills mall parking lot.
你们清理完韦弗家的洪灾了吗
You done cleaning up the Weavers' flood?
没有  只是我们意识到有个更重要的地方
No, we just realized there was someplace more important
我们必须要去
that we needed to be.
非常抱歉  杰西
We're so sorry, Jackie.
只是拥有了全世界
It's just that when you have
最能干的女儿之后
the world's most capable daughter,
很容易就忘了她也需要你
it's easy to forget that she needs you, too.
的确是
Well, she does.
那么告诉我  为什么这个停车场
So...tell me, why is this parking lot
是你在地球最爱的地点之一呢
one of your most favorite places on earth?
我爱的不是停车场
It's not the parking lot.
而是那个十字路口
It's that four-way intersection.
糟糕了
Oh, oh, this will not end well.
我都瞧见了
Now I've seen everything!
你觉得这样的布局
You think a setup like that
肯定会变成大灾难
Would end in constant catastrophe.
但不知为何  每个人都会搞清楚该如何相处
But somehow, everyone figures out how to coexist.
有时人们会落得坏名声
Humans get a bad rap sometimes.
但我发现多半情况
But I've found that more often than not,
他们都能够照顾好其他人
they manage to look out for one another...
在你最意想不到的时候
...and come through for each other
帮助你安然度过困境
when you least expect it.
也许我刚刚说的那些事情
And maybe all those things I just said
并不完全适用于十字路口
don't totally apply to intersections.
但这就是为什么这是地球上我最爱的地点之一
But that is why this is one of my favorite places on earth.
谢谢你和我们分享
Thank you for sharing it with us.
我能明白你为什么喜欢这里
I can see why you love it here.
这是我的荣幸
It's my pleasure.
你们又要走了  是吗
You're leaving again, aren't you?
在邻近的月球上有一个部落
There's a tribe on a neighboring moon
遭受着一场严重的饥荒
that's suffering a terrible famine.
而你父亲  非常擅长灌溉
And your father has such a way with irrigation.
当然  我理解
No, of course. I understand.
拍张照片放在剪贴簿里
For the scrapbook.
我回来啦
I'm home!
这个还在享受信托基金的女婿
And this trust-fund brat of a son-in-law
刚刚自己找到了一个入门级的工...
just got himself an entry-level jo-- oh.
你说过你不想在这里
You said you didn't want to be here
收拾残局  你可以走了
to pick up the pieces, so you can just go.
我亲爱的  你不知道吗
Oh, my darling, don't you know?
帮你收拾残局是我做过的唯一不收费的工作
Picking up your pieces is the only job I'd do for free.
十字路口怎么样
How was the four-way intersection?
没有我是不是不一样了
Not the same without me, right?
完全不同
Not at all.
今天真的好漫长
Really slow day.
你在说谎
You're lying.
我错过了什么
What did I miss?
好吧  好吧
All right, fine.
同时来了四辆车
There were four cars at once.
最终优先权的那辆车不乐意了
The ultimate right-of-way challenge.
好极了
Hot damn!
-跟我描绘一下  -微风徐徐
- Paint the scene for me. - It was a little bit windy.
-接得好  猛虎  -谢了  黛比
- Ooh, great catch, tiger. - Thanks, Debbie.
你看起来容光焕发
You look radiant, by the way.
你一看就像那种男人想要
You look like the kind of girl
共度一生的女孩
a man would want to spend a life with.
你的手臂可以媲美专业棒球手
And you have the arm of a professional ballplayer.
-不一样  -不一样
- It's not the same. - Nope.
-冻酸奶吗  -必须的
- Froyo? - Yeah. Always.